Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Hey!
What the heck're ya doin', Momo?!
Get flyin'!
No... I... I know!
B-But...
M-My body will not move!
D-Do you realize how high up I would be...
were I to so much as raise my head?!
Who cares, dummy?!
You're a grown man and
still scared o' heights?!
Silence!
I will not tolerate insolence!
Th-There is naught we samurai fear!
Then get flyin'!
Fly, dammit!
I cannot, not right this moment!
Later, perhaps...
The hell'd ya grow up for, then?!
You're a dragon!
Fly!
I know that!
Do not hurry me!
We're in a hurry, though!
If we let Kaido run wild around Onigashima,
everyone's gonna be toast!
I understand that!
Alas, my heart is not prepared...
Quit givin' me excuses....
...and fly!
Owowowowowow!
W-Wait, would you?!
Shaddap!
You and me're puttin'
Kaido down, together!
Mirror Mountain.
Defended yourself, huh...
I cannot fall, not yet!
Not until Luffy returns!
All I need do is to
survive until that moment!
Hallowed Glacier Slash!
Look at you...
Challenging me,
like you were one of Wano's own people...
Yamato!
You're an ogre's child!
But you are still the son of Kaido!
You can't run...
...from what's in your blood!
Stop!
No matter what or who
you choose to fight for,
not a single samurai here...
...sees you as one of their own!
Silence!
That has nothing to do...
with how I feel!
You've been living
on this island all alone.
Running around the island,
crawling inside ceilings.
You've been alone your whole life!
But I do...
...have friends!
I have a precious friend!
No...
I had!
So you did.
Like those samurai back then...
Anyone that was ever
nice to you is dead!
No wonder 'tis so cold.
It is snowing...
I am so hungry...
How hungry I am...
There you are, Ogre Princess.
Please wait, Ogre Princess.
You must be hungry.
Here, take it.
Before someone sees, now!
Dig in!
Thank you!
I appreciate it!
Yum...!
So delicious...
Thank you... Thank you...
Good for you, Ogre Princess.
Hey, so why'd he get the axe
all of a sudden?
Heard he was slipping food
to the Ogre Princess.
Even got her a blanket,
thinking she was freezing!
Awww, awful nice of 'im!
The Ogre Princess is still on the run, isn't she?
Saying she wants to become Oden...
They did not simply die.
You murdered them!
They got in the way of me
educating my child.
They deserved it!
You should know better by now...
...Yamato!
You have no friends!
Even if you think those
Wano people're on your side,
that's just on the surface!
They're all afraid of you!
You gotta rule people by force!
And that's because
you're the kid of an ogre!
You can't be friends with humans!
And that's just life for you,
Yamato!
Attaboy, Momo!
I am flying!
Nice!
Keep it up, Momo!
Fly us to Onigashima!
Sally forth!
Go!
Momo!
Goooo!
Onward! Onward!
Man, talk about fast!
Gotta be a dragon thing!
Keep going and we'll
catch up in no time!
We're off-course!
Left!
Momo! More to the left!
Left?!
Ah...
Like this?!
That's it! Attaboy!
All right! Onigashima...
We've caught up!
I see a shadow on the rooftop!
Think that's Kaido!
To the rooftop!
Rooftop?
Understood!
No, no! Not up!
Down!
Down?!
Hey! No! No, no!
Not that way!
Are your eyes even open?!
You buffoon!
How could I possibly fly with eyes open?!
Whaaa?!
No!
This ain't the rooftop!
Three-Sword Style...
What is that?!
A dragon?!
Huh?! Kaido-san?!
No, that's not right!
Huh?! Another dragon?!
Uh? Luffy!
Hit the brakes!
Stop, stop!
Luffy, m'boy!
Luffy!
A sight for sore eyes!
Whoahuhwhaaaa?!
Stop, Momo!
What the hellre ya doing?!
A dragon?!
Kaido, that you?!
Straw Hatter?!
What the hell?!
What's. Going. On?!
Cut it out, dammit!
Open your eyes, Momo!
'Tis impossible!
Besides, something got into them!
That's all 'cause you crashed
into a buncha stuff!
Do something, Luffy!
Show me...
Show me what yer made of
and look in front!
That's a wall!
Braaaakes!
Whaaaa!!
Castle Interior, Third Floor reporting in!
Right now, Kaido-san's on the rampage...
No! That's not him!
Huh?!
But there can't be two dragons!
The color's different, though!
Find out who the pink dragon is!
Pretty damn noisy down there...
Linlin, maybe?
Gonna have to rebuild the castle.
cannot let things...
...end like this!
Divine... Swiftness!
All right!
There he is!
On the rooftop!
Are we there?!
Ah, not good!
We are mid-air!
I must return to solid ground!
There's Kaido!
Right down there,
make a dive for it!
Kaido?!
Gear 48
Snakeman!
Gum-Gum...
Divine Swiftness!
White Serpent!
Jet Culverin!
Eh?!
Luffy!
Oh, Yamabro!
So you're the one that's been
holding off Kaido!
Saved our butts!
Thanks!
A sight for sore eyes!
I have been waiting!
A pink dragon!
It cannot be...!
How in the hell did you live...
Straw Hat?!
How in the hell would I die?
I'm the future Pirate King!
And who the hell's that dragon
supposed to be?
M-My...
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
The future Shogun of Wano!
Enjoying yourself, O-Toko?
Uh-huh!
Where are you going, O-Tama?!
Do you realize the danger
in what you are doing?!
Forgive me, Master!
I can't help it,
I gotta do somethin'!
Don't worry!
We'll protect her with our lives!
O-Tama!
O-Tama, are you faring well?
Alas, she is a sea away...
And I have no way of knowing...
Reporting in,
concerning a mysterious dragon!
On the rooftop, Young Master Yamato
stands alone, bruised and bloodied...
So Yamato was the one
holding off Kaido-san...!
And in the skies,
something unbelievable is taking place...
Two dragons, squaring off!
Facing Kaido-sama,
the Azure Dragon...
...is a pink dragon!
And a pirate upon its back...
Straw Hat Luffy!
The pink dragon's identity
is unknown!
But there is no doubt
it is an enemy of ours!
Momonosuke-kun!
Your form resembles...
...my father!
If I could become a monster such as he,
I would be of some help to everyone...
Momonosuke-kun!
What a surprise!
You're that brat!
But, you see...
...the world ain't big enough
for two dragons!
He is breathing fire!
Amright
you breathe something too!
Breathe what?!
I cannot possibly...!
Momo, you can breathe it!
Humans cannot
simply breathe fire!
Blast Breath!
N-No! I am not here to fight!
Hey, Momo!
Whaaaaat?!
Gear 3!
Wait, Luffy! I cannot, I cannot!
'Tis impossible for me!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Hey, Momo!
Take a bite outta Kaido!
I cannot!
Mother!
All will be well!
I will ensure the two of you escape!
There is a way out of this!
Mother!
Your father was a fool of a lord.
What is your name?!
Tell me!
Mo...
Father!
Kaido!
What're you doing, brat?!
You laid waste to my country!
Were it not for you...
Father would...
Mother would...
Thought I asked you
what the hell you're doing!
Get away, Momonosuke-kun!
Blast Breath!
That's it, Momo!
What?! Momonosuke-sama?!
Momonosuke-sama is a dragon?
A pink one?!
Attaboy, Momonosuke-sama!
That's Kaido you just bit!
Dragons bring
with them thunderclouds...
And there are two dragons here...
That means no more moon tonight.
One more hit from you and
I probably wouldn't be getting up ever again.
The Sulong transformation is a double-edged sword,
feeding on your life force.
It's the end for you, not me.
He lost his Sulong form!
Master Nekomamushi!
Whoa, now!
No butting in!
Don't blame the moon...
It's not like your luck's run out!
Mlem!
It's just that I'm too lucky,
Boss Cat!
Master!
Momo!
You bit...
...an Emperor of the Sea!
There anything left in the world
for ya to be scared of?!
N...
Nay!
Go, Momo!
You can fly!
Aye!
Go stop...
...Onigashima!
As for Kaido,
I'm gonna...
...one hundred percent...
beat him!
Luffy's...
...back in tip-top shape!
Go get 'em, Luffy!
Super!
You hear that?
What a comedian!
Not surprised to
hear that outta him!
Where the hell's he been?
Luffy!
Momo-kun!
Luffy...
When Luffy says he's gonna do something,
he does it!
Big Bro!
Momo-kuuun!
Geez
Get 'em, Luffy!
Finally time, huh...
Yeah, this is just the beginning...
Do you think you have even the
slightest chance of beating me?!
Long as I'm breathin'...
I got all the
chances in the world!
I once read in his journal...
When Roger and Whitebeard clashed...
...the heavens were rent asunder!
Reporting...in...
The heavens... are split...
Say nothing.
Who's luckier meow?
Getting real exciting,
isn't it, Kaido...?
Now...
We've got our own
game to play!
Oden...
...One-Sword Style:
Feline...
...Frenzy!
Worthless pile of dog crap!
Canine...
...Cleaver!
Pedro...
Wish I could knock a few back
with you-gara while moon gazin'...
Master Nekomamushi!
Oh, Carrot!
That was amazing, Master!
Aye!
You've finally done it, Master!
Pedro... would be happy!
All o' you-gara...
Careful now,
or you'll turn Sulong.
Haven't a damn clue why,
...but the moon's
totally out now.
Such is our rage,
all we of the Mink Tribe!
I can hardly believe it!
The Jack is...
I did not expect one of
the All-Stars to be taken down!
Ah, well...
That does not matter to me!